A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1955
  - Guam, 1955; 1955/213
    - Guam (Box 42)
  - Hawaii, 1955; 1955/214
    - Hawaii - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 267)
  - Massachusetts, 1955; 1955/224
    - Massachusetts, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - New York, 1955; 1955/235
    - New York, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Ohio, 1955; 1955/238
    - Ohio, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Pennsylvania, 1955; 1955/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Philippines, 1955; 1955/242
    - Phippines - (A-Sa), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 268)
    - Phippines - Sillman University, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 269)
    - Philippines - (So-Univ. of Philippines/B), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 270)
    - Philippines - (Univ. of Philippines/I-Y), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 271)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/242.A
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1955; 1955/242.C
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/242.D
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/242.E
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/242.R
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Puerto Rico, 1955; 1955/243
    - Puerto Rico - (G-V), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Samoa, 1955; 1955/245
    - Samoa, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 273)
  - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1955; 1955/258
    - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/258.D
      - Trust Territory, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 273)
  - South America, 1955; 1955/300
    - South America & Latin America - Administration, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 274)
    - South America & Latin America - Administration, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 275)
    - South America & Latin America - Administration, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 276)
    - South America & Latin America - Administration - Braga, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 277)
    - South America & Latin America - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 43, Folder 278)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/300.A
      - South America & Latin America (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/300.D
      - South America & Latin America - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/300.E
      - South America & Latin America - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 279)
    - South America - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/300.R
      - South America & Latin America - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 279)
  - Argentina, 1955; 1955/301
    - Argentina - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 280)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/301.A
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 280)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/301.E
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 280)
  - Bolivia, 1955; 1955/303
    - Bolivia, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 281)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/303.E
      - Bolivia, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 281)
  - Brazil, 1955; 1955/305
    - Brazil - (A-B), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 281)
    - Brazil - (C-I), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 282)
    - Brazil - (J-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 283)
    - Brazil - (J-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 284)
    - Brazil - (J-Z), 1955 (Box 44, Folder 285)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/305.A
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1955; 1955/305.C
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/305.D
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/305.E
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Brazil - Malaria, 1955; 1955/305.I
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
    - Brazil - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/305.R
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 286)
  - Chile, 1955; 1955/309
    - Chile - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 287)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/309.A
      - Chile - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 288)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1955; 1955/309.C
      - Chile - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 288)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/309.D
      - Chile - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 288)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/309.E
      - Chile - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 288)
  - Colombia, 1955; 1955/311
    - Colombia - (A-Car), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 289)
    - Colombia - (Cauca Valley Corporation), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 290)
    - Colombia - (Cen-Z), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 291)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/311.A
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 292)
      - Colombia, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 0292A)
      - Colombia, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 415)
    - Colombia - Nursing, 1955; 1955/311.C
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 293)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/311.D
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 293)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/311.E
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 293)
  - Costa Rica, 1955; 1955/313
    - Costa Rica, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 294)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/313.D
      - Costa Rica, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 294)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/313.E
      - Costa Rica, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 294)
        Related Archival Materials note
        See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 313.E.
  - Cuba, 1955; 02.1955/315
    - Cuba, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 294)
    - Cuba - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/315.D
      - Cuba, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 294)
  - Ecuador, 1955; 02.1955/317
    - Ecuador, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
    - Ecuador - Nursing, 1955; 1955/317.C
      - Ecuador, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/317.D
      - Ecuador, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
  - Guatemala, 1955; 1955/319
    - Guatemala, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/319.D
      - Guatemala, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
  - Haiti, 1955; 1955/320
    - Haiti, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
  - Honduras, 1955; 1955/321
    - Honduras, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 295)
  - Mexico, 1955; 1955/323
    - Mexico, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 296)
    - Mexico - (B-I), 1955 (Box 47, Folder 297)
    - Mexico - (K-M), 1955 (Box 47, Folder 298)
    - Mexico - (N-Z), 1955 (Box 47, Folder 299)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/323.A
      - Mexico, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 300)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/323.E
      - Mexico, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 300)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/323.S
      - Mexico, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 300)
  - Nicaragua, 1955; 1955/325
    - Nicaragua, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
    - Nicaragua - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/325.D
      - Nicaragua, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
    - Nicaragua - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/325.E
      - Nicaragua, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
  - Panama, 1955; 1955/327
    - Panama, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
    - Panama - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/327.D
      - Panama, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/327.E
      - Panama, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 301)
  - Paraguay, 1955; 1955/329
    - Paraguay, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 302)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/329.D
      - Paraguay, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 302)
  - Peru, 1955; 1955/331
    - Peru, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/331.A
      - Peru, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/331.D
      - Peru, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/331.E
      - Peru, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
  - El Salvador, 1955; 1955/333
    - El Salvador, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/333.D
      - El Salvador, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/333.E
      - El Salvador, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 303)
  - Uruguay, 1955; 1955/337
    - Uruguay, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Uruguay - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/337.A
      - Uruguay, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/337.D
      - Uruguay, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 304)
  - Venezuela, 1955; 1955/339
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 305)
    - Venezuela, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 415)
    - Venezuela - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/339.A
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Venezuela - Nursing, 1955; 1955/339.C
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/339.D
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/339.E
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Venezuela - Malaria, 1955; 1955/339.I
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
  - Great Britain, 1955; 1955/400
    - Great Britain, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 306)
  - England, 1955; 1955/401
    - England - (A-C), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 307)
    - England - (D-K), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 0307A)
    - England - (L), 1955 (Box 48, Folder 308)
    - England - (M-Op), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 309)
    - England - Oxford University (A-Z), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 310)
    - England - (P-T), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 311)
    - England - University (A-C), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 312)
    - England - University (D-Z), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 313)
    - England - (V-Z), 1955 (Box 49, Folder 314)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/401.A
      - England - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 315)
    - England - Nursing, 1955; 1955/401.C
      - England - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 315)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/401.E
      - England - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 315)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/401.R
      - England - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 315)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/401.S
      - England - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 315)
  - Ireland, 1955; 02.1955/403
    - Ireland, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 316)
    - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/403.E
      - Ireland, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 316)
  - Scotland, 1955; 1955/405
    - Scotland, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 316)
    - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/405.E
      - Scotland, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 316)
  - Wales, 1955; 1955/407
    - Wales, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 316)
  - Australia, 1955; 1955/410
    - Australia - (A-T), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 317)
    - Australia - University (A-T), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 318)
    - Australia - University (W)-Z, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 319)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/410.A
      - Australia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 320)
      - Australia - University of Western Australia, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 415)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/410.E
      - Australia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 50, Folder 320)
  - New Zealand, 1955; 1955/418
    - New Zealand, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 320)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 320)
  - Caribbean Region, 1955; 1955/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 320)
  - Canada, 1955; 1955/427
    - Canada - (A-C), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 321)
    - Canada - (G-Ma), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 322)
    - Canada - (Mc-N), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 323)
    - Canada - (O-U), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 324)
    - Canada - University (A-Z), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 325)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/427.A
      - Canada, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1955; 1955/427.C
      - Canada, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/427.E
      - Canada, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/427.R
      - Canada, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
  - Jamaica, 1955; 1955/437
    - Jamaica, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 326)
  - Trinidad, 1955; 1955/451
    - Trinidad and Tobago - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 51, Folder 327)
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 416)
    - Trinidad - Malaria, 1955; 1955/451.I
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 416)
  - Sri Lanka (Ceylon), 1955; 1955/462
    - Sri Lanka - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 328)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/462.A
      - Sri Lanka, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 328)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/462.E
      - Sri Lanka, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 328)
  - Hong Kong, 1955; 1955/463
    - Hong Kong, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 329)
  - India, 1955; 1955/464
    - India - (A-Al), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 329)
    - India - (An-G), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 330)
    - India - (H-I), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 331)
    - India - (J-N), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 332)
    - India - (P-S), 1955 (Box 52, Folder 333)
    - India - (T-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 334)
    - India - Madia, C. K., 1955 (Box 66, Folder 417)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/464.A
      - India - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 335)
    - India - Nursing, 1955; 1955/464.C
      - India - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 335)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/464.D
      - India - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 335)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/464.E
      - India - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 335)
      - India - (A-Z), 1955; r (Box 53, Folder 336)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/464.R
      - India - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 336)
  - Pakistan, 1955; 1955/465
    - Pakistan, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 337)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/465.D
      - Pakistan, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 337)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/465.E
      - Pakistan, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 337)
    - Pakistan - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/465.R
      - Pakistan, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 337)
  - Burma, 1955; 1955/468
    - Burma, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
    - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/468.A
      - Burma, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
    - Burma - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/468.D
      - Burma, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
  - Iraq, 1955; 1955/470
    - Iraq, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
    - Iraq - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/470.D
      - Iraq, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
    - Iraq - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/470.E
      - Iraq, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1955; 1955/470.I
      - Iraq, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 338)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1955; 1955/472
    - New Guinea and Papua - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 339)
  - Malaysia, 1955; 1955/473
    - Malaysia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 53, Folder 339)
    - Malaysia - University of Malaya - Caine, S., 1955 (Box 66, Folder 418)
    - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/473.A
      - Malaysia, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 339)
  - Africa, 1955; 1955/475
    - Africa, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 339)
    - Africa - "Resources and Needs for Training Facilities for Africans in British Africa, Ethiopia and Liberia", 9/30/1955; 1 (Box 53, Folder 340)
    - Africa - "Resources and Needs for Training Facilities for Africans in British Africa, Ethiopia and Liberia", 9/30/1955; 2 (Box 54, Folder 341)
    - Africa - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
    - Africa - Conference For Technical Research in Africa South of the Sahara, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 419)
    - Africa - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/475.A
      - Africa - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
    - Africa - Health Services, 1955; 1955/475.K
      - Africa - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/475.S
      - Africa - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
  - East Africa Region, 1955; 1955/477
    - East Africa Region, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
    - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/477.A
      - East Africa Region, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 342)
  - North Africa Region, 1955; 1955/485
    - North Africa Region - (A-Al), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 343)
    - North Africa Region - (Am-C), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 344)
    - North Africa Region - (E-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 345)
    - North Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/485.A
      - North Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
    - North Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/485.D
      - North Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
    - North Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/485.E
      - North Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
    - North Africa Region - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/485.S
      - North Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
  - South Africa Region, 1955; 1955/487
    - South Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
    - South Africa Region - Northern Rhodesia Development, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 420)
    - South Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/487.A
      - South Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
    - South Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/487.E
      - South Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 346)
  - West Africa Region, 1955; 1955/495
    - West Africa Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 347)
    - Nigeria - Education, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 420)
    - West Africa Region - Medical Services, 1955; 1955/495.A
      - West Africa Region, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 347)
  - France, 1955; 1955/500
    - France - (A-Be), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 348)
    - France - (Bi-Ma), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 349)
    - France - (Me-O), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 350)
    - France - (P-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 351)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/500.A
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/500.D
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/500.E
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - France - Declinations, 1955; 1955/500.F
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/500.R
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/500.S
      - France - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
  - French Guiana, 1955; 1955/507
    - French Guiana, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
  - Vietnam, 1955; 1955/509
    - Vietnam, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
  - Cambodia, 1955; 1955/513
    - Cambodia, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 352)
  - Asia, 1955; 1955/600
    - Asia and Far East Region - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 55, Folder 353)
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/600.D
      - Asia and Far East Region, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
    - Asia - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/600.S
      - Asia and Far East Region, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
  - China, 1955; 1955/601
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/601.A
      - China, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
      - China, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
  - Taiwan, 1955; 1955/605
    - Taiwan, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
    - Taiwan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/605.E
      - Taiwan, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
    - Taiwan - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/605.R
      - Taiwan, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 354)
      - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1955; 02.1955/609.A
        - Japan, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - Japan, 1955; 1955/609
    - Japan, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 355)
    - Japan - (A-H), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 356)
    - Japan - (I), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 357)
    - Japan - (J-K), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 358)
    - Japan - (M-Sa), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 359)
    - Japan - (Sc-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 360)
    - Japan - Hashimoto, Y., 1955 (Box 66, Folder 421)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/609.D
      - Japan, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 361)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/609.E
      - Japan, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 361)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/609.R
      - Japan, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - Korea, 1955; 1955/613
    - Korea - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 362)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/613.R
      - Korea, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 362)
  - Thailand, 1955; 1955/617
    - Thailand, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 362)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/617.D
      - Thailand, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 362)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/617.E
      - Thailand, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 362)
  - Southeast Asia, 1955; 1955/625
    - Southeast Asia Region, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 363)
  - Curacao, 1955; 1955/651
    - Curacao - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 363)
    - Curacao - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/651.E
      - Curacao - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 363)
    - Curacao - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/651.S
      - Curacao - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 363)
  - Indonesia, 1955; 1955/652
    - Indonesia - (A-I), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 364)
    - Indonesia - (K-Z), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 365)
    - Indonesia - Education, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 421)
    - Indonesia - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/652.A
      - Indonesia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 366)
    - Indonesia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/652.D
      - Indonesia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 366)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/652.E
      - Indonesia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 366)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/652.R
      - Indonesia - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 366)
  - Surinam, 1955; 1955/659
    - Surinam, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 366)
  - Europe, 1955; 1955/700
    - Europe, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 367)
    - Europe - Societe Europeenne de Culture, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 422)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/700.A
      - Europe, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 367)
  - Afghanistan, 1955; 1955/703
    - Afghanistan, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 367)
    - Afghanistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1955; 1955/703.D
      - Afghanistan, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 367)
  - Austria, 1955; 1955/705
    - Austria - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 368)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/705.E
      - Austria, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 368)
    - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/705.R
      - Austria, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 368)
  - Belgium, 1955; 1955/707
    - Belgium, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 369)
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/707.A
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 369)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1955; 1955/707.C
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 369)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/707.E
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 369)
    - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/707.S